<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diaries on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diaries on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 10:22:45 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #3: Loyalty Ventures Inc</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 10:22:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0003/</guid>
      <description>Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at Loyalty Ventures Inc, $LYLT.
$LYLT was spun off by $ADS in November 2021.
Loyalty Ventures Inc owns and operate the AIR MILES® Reward Program, Canada’s most recognized loyalty program, and Netherlands-based BrandLoyalty, a global provider of purpose-driven, tailor-made, campaign-based loyalty solutions for grocers and other high-frequency retailers.
EPS as of 2021Q3 were $0.97 for the quarter and $2.34 YTD, or about $3.1 annualized, giving us around ~10x P/E at the current share price of $32.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #2: Semler Scientific</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 07:11:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0002/</guid>
      <description>The bull argument Last week, I listened to an interview of Yen Liow on The Equity Mates podcast. What a fascinating character, the passion for finding and investing in great companies exudes out of him.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the interview if you&amp;rsquo;re interested:
  He was generous enough to pitch two stocks during the interview, one of them being Semler Scientific $SMLR.
Semler Scientific owns a product called QuantaFlo, which is a cloud-supported easy-to-use PAD test kit that delivers fast and accurate results in less than 5-minutes at the point-of-care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #1: Texas Pacific Land Corp</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 07:28:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0001/</guid>
      <description>TPL I just listened to a fascinating interview of Steven Bregman, President and co-founder of Horizon Kinetics. Here&amp;rsquo;s a short description of this firm: &amp;ldquo;dedicated to long-horizon, creative approaches to investing, away from mass-market, asset allocation driven orthodoxy&amp;rdquo;. Pretty cool, huh!
The interview was mainly about the index investing bubble. Steven did a great job explaining the mechanics of that bubble. You can watch the interview here.
Towards the end, Steven talks about one of his main holdings: Texas Land Corporation, $TPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #0: The Purpose</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0000/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 07:20:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0000/</guid>
      <description>Aswath Damodaran, who has been christened as the &amp;ldquo;Dean of Valuation&amp;rdquo; due to his deep expertise on the topic, has said: &amp;ldquo;Valuation is neither a science nor an art. It is a craft.&amp;quot;
I believe that to be true, and more than ever, I want to practice this craft.
But I want to do it publicly, because I think it can be of value to others who might want to go down this path.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
