<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Guy Spier: The Education of a Value Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal summary of Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book. I take the liberty of mixing snippets from the book with my own thoughts.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting the book, here&amp;rsquo;s the amazon link. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it enough.
Ch 1: Know what game you (and others) are playing Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axiom #1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</guid>
      <description>Principles are important because they can make hard decisions easier. So they are useful from an efficiency standpoint.
They can also serve to lower the chances of catastrophic mistakes. If you draft your principles when your mind is at rest, what you come up with will likely help protect you from emotional impulses when you are in a more tumultuous frame of mind.
However I don&amp;rsquo;t think that principles are the foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
