<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:06:24 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maxing Out Positions</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/maxing-out-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:06:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/maxing-out-positions/</guid>
      <description>Just read this fantastic post from Kuppy.
I absolutely love how he discards all the unpredictable and risky stuff that sometimes passes for desirable asymetry, whereas it&amp;rsquo;s just unknowable shit that could go either way. Noise.
I do agree with him on Uranium. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it in multiple places. France is one example, because I follow the run-up to the presidential election. Both the incumbent (Macron) and the one I see as his strongest opponent (Eric Zemmour) are pro uranium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversation with Artem Fokin</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/artem-fokin-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 13:10:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/artem-fokin-conversation/</guid>
      <description>These are some notes I took listening to a CO/nversations podcast episode featuring Artem Fokin, from Caro-Kann Capital LLC. I enjoyed it, and Artem is clearly a smart and thoughtful guy.
  Be more demanding on the upside. Look for plausible 4x to 5x baggers. 50% upside is lame. Because you can be wrong, management&amp;rsquo;s execution can be off, bad luck can happen&amp;hellip;so you end up with +20% after a few years, which sucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Approach</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</guid>
      <description>Update (2021-09-08) I was trying a bit too hard when writing this post. In a sense, that&amp;rsquo;s to be expected when one is still trying to find their style.
I want to share a beautiful post that resonated strongly with me and that explains much better the ideas that I tried to convey here. The post&amp;rsquo;s title is Peak Quality?, and you can read it here.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my favorite quote from that post:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Principles for Investing and Life</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:07:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</guid>
      <description>Webcast featuring William Green (@williamgreen72), Guy Spier (@GSpier) and Matthias Knab (@MatthiasKnab).
I have read and greatly benefitted from Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book &amp;ldquo;The Education of a Value Investor&amp;rdquo; and have just received William&amp;rsquo;s highly praised &amp;ldquo;Richer, Wiser, Happier&amp;rdquo;, which is next on my reading list.
Here are my takeaways from the webinar: 7 Key principles for investing and life
1. Cloning Mohnish Pabrai: &amp;ldquo;Everything in my life is cloned - I have no original ideas&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guy Spier: The Education of a Value Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal summary of Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book. I take the liberty of mixing snippets from the book with my own thoughts.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting the book, here&amp;rsquo;s the amazon link. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it enough.
Ch 1: Know what game you (and others) are playing Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
