<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:12:22 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investing Approach</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</guid>
      <description>Foreword I really struggle to figure out how or why I would have an edge investing in the market. To some degree, and as far as comparing myself to the market, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter that much. In the sense that I don&amp;rsquo;t mind underperforming any given index, as long as I&amp;rsquo;m learning and having fun.
But I feel that the only way I can learn efficiently is by leaning on my strengths, and that&amp;rsquo;s why I think about what my edge could be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Principles for Investing and Life</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:07:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</guid>
      <description>Webcast featuring William Green (@williamgreen72), Guy Spier (@GSpier) and Matthias Knab (@MatthiasKnab).
I have read and greatly benefitted from Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book &amp;ldquo;The Education of a Value Investor&amp;rdquo; and have just received William&amp;rsquo;s highly praised &amp;ldquo;Richer, Wiser, Happier&amp;rdquo;, which is next on my reading list.
Here are my takeaways from the webinar: 7 Key principles for investing and life
1. Cloning Mohnish Pabrai: &amp;ldquo;Everything in my life is cloned - I have no original ideas&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guy Spier: The Education of a Value Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal summary of Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book. I take the liberty of mixing snippets from the book with my own thoughts.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting the book, here&amp;rsquo;s the amazon link. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it enough.
Ch 1: Know what game you (and others) are playing Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
