<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:23:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Even God would get fired as an Active Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:23:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0016/</guid>
      <description>An interesting study on the theoretical return of a God-like active investor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned in 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/what-i-learned-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:07:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/what-i-learned-2021/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t be an ideologue   Keep religion and dogma out of your financial decisions.
  Be mindful of cognitive rigidity, and commitment and consistency bias.
  Don&amp;rsquo;t be arrogant. If you get spanked on the market, you might want to regroup and reassess. Maybe the market is trying to teach you something. Don&amp;rsquo;t do this.
  Emotions are good if used properly. Use pain to learn from your own mistakes and envy to learn from the successes of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Munger Is the Goat</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/munger-is-the-goat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 18:30:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/munger-is-the-goat/</guid>
      <description>Today I stumbled on this tweet:
🧵 of what Munger said this week: “It’s getting very difficult because we have a vast increase in the intellectual horsepower that’s trying to get rich by owning securities,” pic.twitter.com/ljmpQdDVPX
&amp;mdash; Andrew Hollingworth (@andrewhollingw) December 4, 2021  This is stuch a powerful, crystal clear chain of thought. Probably the reason why it resonated so much with me is that I was thinking something along these lines but it was way more blurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/thanksgiving-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 11:28:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/thanksgiving-2021/</guid>
      <description>Today was a rough day on the markets. A new variant has been detected in South Africa, and it seems to be a vicious one with a lot of mutations in the right (or wrong, depending how you look at it) places. It seems like it has very high transmissibility, but we don&amp;rsquo;t know much yet about its severity and how easily it can escape the current vaccines.
As of the time of this writing, the S&amp;amp;P is down 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeBABAcle</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/debabacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 13:41:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/debabacle/</guid>
      <description>$BABA have released their earnings, and the market didn&amp;rsquo;t like them. I didn&amp;rsquo;t look into the details of it, but basically growth and margin have slowed down in their core commerce business due to competitive pressures. Cloud is growing nicely, but not much impact on the bottom-line yet.
A few days prior, we learned that Pabrai had sold the majority of his stake. This had a liberating effect on me: I wondered &amp;ldquo;Why am I in this position to begin with?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Value Investors</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/value-investing-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 19:29:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/value-investing-resources/</guid>
      <description>This list is by no means intended to be comprehensive, and it will most likely grow with time. These are just a few links that I find useful and that fit my style and what I&amp;rsquo;m looking for in terms of investment content. I also focus on the free stuff, because I&amp;rsquo;m a cheap fuck.
Insider Transactions US   Bezinga
  Tipranks
  OpenInsider
  InsiderTrades</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maxing Out Positions</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/maxing-out-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:06:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/maxing-out-positions/</guid>
      <description>Just read this fantastic post from Kuppy.
I absolutely love how he discards all the unpredictable and risky stuff that sometimes passes for desirable asymetry, whereas it&amp;rsquo;s just unknowable shit that could go either way. Noise.
I do agree with him on Uranium. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it in multiple places. France is one example, because I follow the run-up to the presidential election. Both the incumbent (Macron) and the one I see as his strongest opponent (Eric Zemmour) are pro uranium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversation with Artem Fokin</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/artem-fokin-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 13:10:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/artem-fokin-conversation/</guid>
      <description>These are some notes I took listening to a CO/nversations podcast episode featuring Artem Fokin, from Caro-Kann Capital LLC. I enjoyed it, and Artem is clearly a smart and thoughtful guy.
  Be more demanding on the upside. Look for plausible 4x to 5x baggers. 50% upside is lame. Because you can be wrong, management&amp;rsquo;s execution can be off, bad luck can happen&amp;hellip;so you end up with +20% after a few years, which sucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Approach</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/investing-approach/</guid>
      <description>Update (2021-09-08) I was trying a bit too hard when writing this post. In a sense, that&amp;rsquo;s to be expected when one is still trying to find their style.
I want to share a beautiful post that resonated strongly with me and that explains much better the ideas that I tried to convey here. The post&amp;rsquo;s title is Peak Quality?, and you can read it here.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my favorite quote from that post:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Principles for Investing and Life</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:07:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/key-principles/</guid>
      <description>Webcast featuring William Green (@williamgreen72), Guy Spier (@GSpier) and Matthias Knab (@MatthiasKnab).
I have read and greatly benefitted from Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book &amp;ldquo;The Education of a Value Investor&amp;rdquo; and have just received William&amp;rsquo;s highly praised &amp;ldquo;Richer, Wiser, Happier&amp;rdquo;, which is next on my reading list.
Here are my takeaways from the webinar: 7 Key principles for investing and life
1. Cloning Mohnish Pabrai: &amp;ldquo;Everything in my life is cloned - I have no original ideas&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guy Spier: The Education of a Value Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal summary of Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book. I take the liberty of mixing snippets from the book with my own thoughts.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting the book, here&amp;rsquo;s the amazon link. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it enough.
Ch 1: Know what game you (and others) are playing Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
