<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Takeaways: The Education of a Value Investor (Guy Spier)</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>Ch 1: Different games Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.
If somone wants to sell you something, they will first make it sound like they&amp;rsquo;re playing the same game as you. If someone is trying to make it sound like they&amp;rsquo;re playing the same game as you, they are likely trying to sell you something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sold $CTS.TO</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/trimmed-cts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 17:46:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/trimmed-cts/</guid>
      <description>In a nutshell Connor Haley (Alta Fox Capital) made a presentation (video and slides) about multi-baggers.
It turns out two thirds of the performance of multi-baggers comes from multiple expansion, and one third from EBITDA growth.
In the case of $CTS.TO I&amp;rsquo;ve extracted as much as I can reasonably expect from multiple expansion, and I see risk on the EBITDA front going forward.
Risk vs uncertainty I sold ~most~ all of my $CTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 21:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</guid>
      <description>I need to flush out everything I can about the Nuran thing. Rub my nose in it. And then hopefully come out cleaner on the other side.
This is the first post. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s the last one.
What happened I don&amp;rsquo;t remember much about the day when I bought the bulk of my Nuran position.
But I do remember the moment when I was buying. It felt like nothing else existed except for me and this stock I desired so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axiom #1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</guid>
      <description>Principles are important because they can make hard decisions easier. So they are useful from an efficiency standpoint.
They can also serve to lower the chances of catastrophic mistakes. If you draft your principles when your mind is at rest, what you come up with will likely help protect you from emotional impulses when you are in a more tumultuous frame of mind.
However I don&amp;rsquo;t think that principles are the foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
