<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>diary on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diary on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:53:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #7: Oil - take 2</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:53:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0007/</guid>
      <description>After saying that I spent too much time thinking about energy and oil stocks these past few days, I spent the weekend pretty much thinking only about it.
I was mainly thinking about the current global situation we&amp;rsquo;re in.
Interestingly, I did not think about the kind of returns I could make or miss by betting or not on the sector. I was more intellectually attracted by the situation itself. Which is a good sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #6: Aimia Inc</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:53:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0006/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I looked at Loyalty Ventures Inc, the AirMiles company. While the company itself was not attractive for me as an investment, I learned a thing or two about the customer loyalty space. One of these learnings is that frequent flyer points are much more valuable within an airline company than outside of it.
From there, a bit more research online has led me to an interesting event-driven situation and potential investment opportunity that involves an airline in trouble and its frequent flyer points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #5: Oil and Gas</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:04:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0005/</guid>
      <description>This post will be slightly more philosophical in nature and a bit longer than usual. To make up for that, I promise some concrete take-aways and action items.
Two concepts I&amp;rsquo;d like to explore:
  the concept of &amp;ldquo;circle of competence&amp;rdquo;, its implications and misuses
  why opportunities exist
  Circle of Competence Buffet has popularized the importance of staying within our circle of competence when it comes to investing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #4: Loyalty Ventures Inc</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0004/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:22:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0004/</guid>
      <description>Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at Loyalty Ventures Inc, $LYLT.
$LYLT was spun off by Alliance Data Systems ($ADS) in November 2021.
Loyalty Ventures Inc owns and operates the AIR MILES® Reward Program, Canada’s most recognized loyalty program, and Netherlands-based BrandLoyalty, a global provider of purpose-driven, tailor-made, campaign-based loyalty solutions for grocers and other high-frequency retailers.
EPS as of 2021Q3 was $0.97 for the quarter and $2.34 for the 9mo YTD, or about $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #3: WildBrain</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:39:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0003/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I own shares of this company. None of this is investment advice. I do not know your particular situation and I am not qualified to give you advice. Please do your own due diligence.
This will probably be the first in a series of posts on WildBrain. My goal here is just to give a taste of what I like about the company, but there&amp;rsquo;s much more to the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #2: Semler Scientific</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 07:11:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0002/</guid>
      <description>The bull argument Last week, I listened to an interview of Yen Liow on The Equity Mates podcast. What a fascinating character, the passion for finding and investing in great companies exudes out of him.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the interview if you&amp;rsquo;re interested:
  He was generous enough to pitch two stocks during the interview, one of them being Semler Scientific $SMLR.
Semler Scientific owns a product called QuantaFlo, which is a cloud-supported easy-to-use PAD test kit that delivers fast and accurate results in less than 5-minutes at the point-of-care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #1: Texas Pacific Land Corp</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 07:28:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0001/</guid>
      <description>TPL I just listened to a fascinating interview of Steven Bregman, President and co-founder of Horizon Kinetics. Here&amp;rsquo;s a short description of this firm: &amp;ldquo;dedicated to long-horizon, creative approaches to investing, away from mass-market, asset allocation driven orthodoxy&amp;rdquo;. Pretty cool, huh!
The interview was mainly about the index investing bubble. Steven did a great job explaining the mechanics of that bubble. You can watch the interview here.
Towards the end, Steven talks about one of his main holdings: Texas Land Corporation, $TPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Diary - Issue #0: The Purpose</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0000/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 07:20:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0000/</guid>
      <description>Aswath Damodaran, who has been christened as the &amp;ldquo;Dean of Valuation&amp;rdquo; due to his deep expertise on the topic, has said: &amp;ldquo;Valuation is neither a science nor an art. It is a craft.&amp;quot;
I believe that to be true, and more than ever, I want to practice this craft.
But I want to do it publicly, because I think it can be of value to others who might want to go down this path.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
