<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:04:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/about/</guid>
      <description>sadfsadf sadf sa fsd fds</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goedeker</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/goedeker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:04:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/goedeker/</guid>
      <description>Bottom-line upfront At $3, seems cheap to me. Almost free option on the upside&amp;hellip;
Some details The latest revenue figures:
Full diluted share count: 197.8M
Forecasted 2021 EBITDA: $60M
Net cash: $257.1M
Net Working Capital: -$29.9M
Market cap @ 3.20$: $633.2M
==&amp;gt; EV: $406.0M
==&amp;gt; Forecasted EV/EBITDA: 6.7x
Here&amp;rsquo;s a tweet from @capy_capital with the details:
At share price of:
 $4: EV = $564.0M, EV/EBITDA = 9.4x $5: EV = $761.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 3</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 17:50:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-3/</guid>
      <description>Like I said in the previous NuRAN posts here and here, $NUR.CN started as an oversized speculative bet.
To this day, having this much capital tied up in one entity that has still to prove itself execution-wise is frustrating.
In the past few days however, the company has suprisingly announced three Memorandums of Understanding:
 with Telinno Consulting in Mali (West Africa) for 150 sites with Sierra Tel in Sierra Leone (West Africa) for 125 sites with MTN in South Sudan for 250 sites  The timelines for the definitive agreements are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Stearns - Personality of Success</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/personality-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 11:16:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/personality-of-success/</guid>
      <description>This is a summary of a truly fantastic episode of the &amp;ldquo;Grit Happens&amp;rdquo; podcast, featuring Glenn Stearns, founder and CEO of Kind Lending.
  This episode was shared to me by Sean Iddings as it pertains to $EXPI and SUCCESS Lending, a joint venture between eXp World Holdings and Kind Lending. In other words, this is the baby of not one but two intelligent fanatics.
Below are my takeaways from that episode, as I find it easier to retain inforrmation when I read/write it than when I hear it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guy Spier: The Education of a Value Investor</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 11:18:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/book-guy-spier/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal summary of Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s wonderful book. I take the liberty of mixing snippets from the book with my own thoughts.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting the book, here&amp;rsquo;s the amazon link. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it enough.
Ch 1: Know what game you (and others) are playing Everyone is playing a different game.
The one they appear to be playing is not always the one they are really playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viemed</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/viemed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 11:33:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/viemed/</guid>
      <description>Why I&amp;rsquo;m exiting I had a small position in Viemed because it&amp;rsquo;s a company with strong growth, a strong moat and a deep runway.
I decided to sell because, for one, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be in that space anymore, i.e. selling services to dying people.
But more importantly, I initially had overlooked the compensation of top executives. Top-5 executives compensation was 7.4% of revenues in 2019. I don&amp;rsquo;t like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converge Technologies</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/cts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 17:46:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/cts/</guid>
      <description>In a nutshell Connor Haley (Alta Fox Capital) made a presentation (video and slides) about multi-baggers.
It turns out two thirds of the performance of multi-baggers comes from multiple expansion, and one third from EBITDA growth.
In the case of $CTS.TO I&amp;rsquo;ve extracted as much as I can reasonably expect from multiple expansion, and I see risk on the EBITDA front going forward.
Risk vs uncertainty I sold ~most~ all of my $CTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 2</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:08:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-2/</guid>
      <description>In my first post about Nuran, I talked a lot about my internal and external environment, internal being my feelings (frustration, envy, greed), and external being my work setting, the information I expose myself to, etc.
Today I learned two new things from Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s book.
Commitment bias The first one is the danger that comes with publicly sharing your current positions. I already had a feeling about this one but reading Guy&amp;rsquo;s explanation and detailed examples made me realize I&amp;rsquo;m not careful enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 21:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</guid>
      <description>I need to flush out everything I can about the Nuran thing. Rub my nose in it. And then hopefully come out cleaner on the other side.
This is the first post. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s the last one.
What happened I don&amp;rsquo;t remember much about the day when I bought the bulk of my Nuran position.
But I do remember the moment when I was buying. It felt like nothing else existed except for me and this stock I desired so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of competence vs shameless cloning</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 13:52:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/shameless-cloning/</guid>
      <description>The concept of circle of competence is well known in the investing community. I believe it was popularized by Warren Buffet, at least that&amp;rsquo;s how I first came accross it. Both Buffet and Munger have emphasized endless times to invest only in what you understand. And they&amp;rsquo;re not the only ones, other super investors like Peter Lynch have hammered the idea of leveraging whatever expertise you possess to make good investment by remaining within your circle of competence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update June 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-june-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-june-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preliminary remark I purposely refrain from sharing my portfolio updates on social media. First, because no one cares. Sharing would just put me in a position to care about the fact that no one cares, and that would be a waste of mental energy. Second, this is only my second year of investing seriously (we could even argue that 2020 doesn&amp;rsquo;t count) so there&amp;rsquo;s really not much to share anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Straight</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/thinking-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:29:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/thinking-straight/</guid>
      <description>Being right vs thinking straight I saw this today on twitter:
While I agree that market dislocations (between price and value) naturally occur more frequently in the micro and small cap universe, they can also be found with large caps.
But more importantly, whether I agree with the point or not, the argument (highlighted in the screenshot) does not by itself support the conclusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Madness</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:46:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</guid>
      <description>My wife found a house she likes for sale today. Asking price around $550K. House has been on the market for one day.
The realtor told her there are already 60 visits scheduled. There are only 2 spots left. You only get 15 mins, and only one person can visit per household.
This is nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 12:24:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/baba/</guid>
      <description>Thesis Summary Updated version:
The cloud. 60% growth. Population just coming online. Businesses will go straight to the cloud (no on premise). Invisible in the earnings as of today. High margins (AWS ~ 30% operating margin).
Previous version:
Charlie Munger bought some (19% of The Daily Journal&amp;rsquo;s portfolio). The last time he bought something was in 2014. Mohnish Pabrai is partaking. The current price is lower than when either of them bought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update May 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-may-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 14:33:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-may-2021/</guid>
      <description>Below is the portfolio&amp;rsquo;s performance YTD (time-weighted cumulative return). The month&amp;rsquo;s performances assume cashflows occured mid-month. USD holdings are excluded but quite small at the moment.
The positive performance was driven mainly by CTS.TO which has been a great holding so far (up more than 100% since first purchase), and NUR.CN which is down around 30% since first purchase but made a nice comeback this month. The big losers were PBX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axiom #1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</guid>
      <description>Principles are important because they can make hard decisions easier. So they are useful from an efficiency standpoint.
They can also serve to lower the chances of catastrophic mistakes. If you draft your principles when your mind is at rest, what you come up with will likely help protect you from emotional impulses when you are in a more tumultuous frame of mind.
However I don&amp;rsquo;t think that principles are the foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you know?</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/iknow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 13:14:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/iknow/</guid>
      <description>What do you know? Today, I had this exchange with a fellow fintwitter:
The highlighted statement reminds sounds to me like: &amp;ldquo;I know that Jesus will come back&amp;rdquo;
I guess people like to use the word &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; to make their convictions sound like certainties.
As of today, although it&amp;rsquo;s likely that Bitcoin will play some kind of role in the future, there is nothing knowable about what that role will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Communications Management</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 10:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</guid>
      <description>Bottom line up front I am not taking a position in DCM as of today. While the stock is cheap in terms of multiples, the company is in the declining printing business and they need a mini-miracle to expand out of it into digital. I do not see a clear path towards a 10 bagger in 5 years.
The cannabis labeling business represents only 5% of their revenues despite their market leader position in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
