<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:46:49 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/about/</guid>
      <description>sadfsadf sadf sa fsd fds</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Madness</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:46:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</guid>
      <description>My wife found a house she likes for sale today. Asking price around $550K. House has been on the market for one day.
The realtor told her there are already 60 visits scheduled. There are only 2 spots left. You only get 15 mins, and only one person can visit per household.
This is nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment thesis: $BABA</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/purchased-baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 12:24:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/purchased-baba/</guid>
      <description>Thesis Summary Charlie Munger bought some (19% of The Daily Journal&amp;rsquo;s portfolio). The last time he bought something was in 2014. Mohnish Pabrai is partaking. The current price is lower than when either of them bought. Sentiment on the stock is probably near peak pessimism. Valuation is cheap. Growth, optionality, FCF and balance sheet are very strong.
Quantitative $BABA is growing at ~30% YoY and trading at near all-time lows of:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - May 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-may-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 14:33:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/portfolio-may-2021/</guid>
      <description>Below is the portfolio&amp;rsquo;s performance YTD (time-weighted cumulative return). The month&amp;rsquo;s performances assume cashflows occured mid-month. USD holdings are excluded but quite small at the moment.
The positive performance was driven mainly by CTS.TO which has been a great holding so far (up more than 100% since first purchase), and NUR.CN which is down around 30% since first purchase but made a nice comeback this month. The big losers were PBX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axiom #1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/axiom-1/</guid>
      <description>Principles are important because they can make hard decisions easier. So they are useful from an efficiency standpoint.
They can also serve to lower the chances of catastrophic mistakes. If you draft your principles when your mind is at rest, what you come up with will likely help protect you from emotional impulses when you are in a more tumultuous frame of mind.
However I don&amp;rsquo;t think that principles are the foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you know?</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/iknow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 13:14:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/iknow/</guid>
      <description>What do you know? Today, I had this exchange with a fellow fintwitter:
The highlighted statement reminds sounds to me like: &amp;ldquo;I know that Jesus will come back&amp;rdquo;
I guess people like to use the word &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; to make their convictions sound like certainties.
As of today, although it&amp;rsquo;s likely that Bitcoin will play some kind of role in the future, there is nothing knowable about what that role will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$DCM - buying opportunity?</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 10:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</guid>
      <description>Bottom line up front I am not taking a position in DCM as of today. While the stock is cheap in terms of multiples, the company is in the declining printing business and they need a mini-miracle to expand out of it into digital. I do not see a clear path towards a 10 bagger in 5 years.
The cannabis labeling business represents only 5% of their revenues despite their market leader position in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
