<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>the greats on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/the-greats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in the greats on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:21:56 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/the-greats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adam Robinson on The Business Brew</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/adam-robinson-bizbrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:21:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/adam-robinson-bizbrew/</guid>
      <description>Notes from an awesome podcast episode of The Busines Brew, featuring Adam Robinson.
  This one was not easy to digest, as Adam touches on A LOT of topics. I did my best to capture it all but I got tired near the end, so surely I missed some.
Everything here is just a write-down of Adam&amp;rsquo;s ideas. If you spot a mistake, please let me know.
Confirmation Bias We all attempt to make sense of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Moglia</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/joe-moglia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:19:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/joe-moglia/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I am a shareholder of $OPFI. That&amp;rsquo;s how I first heard of coach Joe Moglia.
These are my notes from this episode of the Co/Investor Club podcast featuring Joe Moglia.
About Joe Moglia Joe is the former CEO and Chairman of TD Ameritrade, former head football coach of Coastal Carolina University, chairman of Fundamental Global Investors and Capital Wealth Advisors, chairman of FGNA (now $OPFI), Executive Advisor to the President of Coastal Carolina University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Stearns</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/glenn-stearns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 11:16:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/glenn-stearns/</guid>
      <description>This is a summary of a truly fantastic episode of the &amp;ldquo;Grit Happens&amp;rdquo; podcast, featuring Glenn Stearns, founder and CEO of Kind Lending.
  This episode was shared to me by Sean Iddings as it pertains to $EXPI and SUCCESS Lending, a joint venture between eXp World Holdings and Kind Lending. In other words, this is the baby of not one but two intelligent fanatics.
Below are my takeaways from that episode, as I find it easier to retain inforrmation when I read/write it than when I hear it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
