<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>random on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/random/</link>
    <description>Recent content in random on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 19:48:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/random/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the pandemic and the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/vaccine-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 19:48:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/vaccine-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>My goal in this post is to write down my reasons for not taking the vaccine (as of today).
This is a heated conversation currently, and I&amp;rsquo;m seeing a lot of people being unnecessarily extreme in their comments on the subject.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example coming from a very smart person:
I want to try and avoid such biased and extreme stances, and make my decisions while considering both sides of any issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Write</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/why-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:02:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/why-write/</guid>
      <description>Why do I write, and why do I publish on this lame page that nobody knows about?
Let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can explain. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that writing this piece will help me understand why I write in general.
I think the answer is: ego.
I am reminded of this movie called Revolver by Guy Ritchie, the director of Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels and Snatch, among others.
The movie is a kind of complicated metaphor about the invisible power of the ego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Madness</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:46:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</guid>
      <description>My wife found a house she likes for sale today. Asking price around $550K. House has been on the market for one day.
The realtor told her there are already 60 visits scheduled. There are only 2 spots left. You only get 15 mins, and only one person can visit per household.
This is nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
