<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>random on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/random/</link>
    <description>Recent content in random on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:10:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/random/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Friday Musings</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:10:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/diary/investing-diary-0010/</guid>
      <description>News bite A sad story out of Canada:
 In an e-mail viewed by CTV News Toronto, a representative from Mount Sinai Hospital told Di Maria her surgery was cancelled because of &amp;ldquo;the situation with COVID-19&amp;rdquo; and that &amp;ldquo;everything is getting cancelled at this point.&amp;rdquo;
 It seems like hospitals are overwhelmed. Anything non-covid related is likely to be postponed. Something to keep in mind if considering investments in MedTech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes (growing)</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:58:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/quotes/</guid>
      <description>A wise man&amp;rsquo;s life is based around FUCK YOU. The Gambler 
You know how I stayed alive this long, all these years? Fear. The spectacle of fearsome acts. Bill the Butcher - Gangs Of New York 
I knew him as a man. I knew his weakness and his strength. But if you ask me &amp;ldquo;will we ever see his like again?&amp;rdquo;, I would say no. Bjorn Goes Into Battle One Last Time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the pandemic and the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/vaccine-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 19:48:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/vaccine-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE (2021-12-09) To boost or not to boost If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following me and reading my crazy midnight tweets, you know I was hesitant to vaccinate initially (because of unknown risks), but I did it after some time.
Today (with Omicron), unless you&amp;rsquo;re high risk, I think going down the vaccine route is a mistake.
Keep in mind, I don&amp;rsquo;t know anything about virology.
You might say, &amp;ldquo;how dare you talk about this stuff if you&amp;rsquo;re not an expert&amp;rdquo;, and I would argue that there are plenty (too many) non-experts pushing to vaccinate blindly, so I don&amp;rsquo;t feel bad voicing a dissenting opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Write</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/why-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:02:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/why-write/</guid>
      <description>Satisfying my ego Why do I write, and why do I publish on this lame page that nobody knows about?
Let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can explain. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that writing this piece will help me understand why I write in general.
I think the answer is: ego.
I am reminded of this movie called Revolver by Guy Ritchie, the director of Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels and Snatch, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Madness</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:46:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/housing-market/</guid>
      <description>My wife found a house she likes for sale today. Asking price around $550K. House has been on the market for one day.
The realtor told her there are already 60 visits scheduled. There are only 2 spots left. You only get 15 mins, and only one person can visit per household.
This is nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
