<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stocks on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stocks on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:53:52 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sunlight Financial $SUNL</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/sunlight-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:53:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/sunlight-financial/</guid>
      <description>Company Overview Sunlight (NYSE:SUNL) is a business-to-business-to-consumer, technology-enabled point-of-sale (“POS”) financing platform that provides residential solar and home improvement contractors the ability to offer seamless POS financing to their customers when purchasing residential solar systems or other home improvements. The resulting loans are funded by Sunlight’s network of capital providers who, by partnering with Sunlight, gain access to a difficult-toreach loan market, best-in-class consumer credit underwriting and attractive risk adjusted returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlas Engineering Products</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/aep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:53:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/aep/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: As of the date of writing this post, I am long the stock discussed here. This is not investment advice, and is intended for informational purposes only. Please do your own due diligence.
This is a quickly written overview of the stock &amp;amp; the business. For a more detailed write-up, check it out this post from Luc Nadeau.
The stock ticker is $AEP.V. The company builds and sells manufactured roof trusses and other engineered building products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jakks</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/jakks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 21:35:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/jakks/</guid>
      <description>Full credits to: @Plum_Capital
Share price: $13
Market cap 6.4M shares outstanding (as of May 10, 2021) + 3.35M shares in convertibles + 195K shares converted as per June 3rd PR = 10M shares (source: seekingalpha).
==&amp;gt; MC (fully diluted) = $130M
Cash  $84M cash, minus $3.6M of restricted = $80.4M $6.7M of short-term debt Old Term Loan $128.9M @ 10.5% New Term Loan $99M (matures June 2027) @ LIBOR+700BPS Unknown refinancing costs (say ~$5M) Preferred $20M @ 6%  ==&amp;gt; net debt (excl WC) ~ $80M</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goedeker</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/goedeker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:04:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/goedeker/</guid>
      <description>Bottom-line upfront At $3, seems cheap to me. Almost free option on the upside&amp;hellip;
Some details The latest revenue figures:
Full diluted share count: 197.8M
Forecasted 2021 EBITDA: $60M
Net cash: $257.1M
Net Working Capital: -$29.9M
Market cap @ 3.20$: $633.2M
==&amp;gt; EV: $406.0M
==&amp;gt; Forecasted EV/EBITDA: 6.7x
Here&amp;rsquo;s a tweet from @capy_capital with the details:
At share price of:
 $4: EV = $564.0M, EV/EBITDA = 9.4x $5: EV = $761.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 3</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 17:50:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-3/</guid>
      <description>Like I said in the previous NuRAN posts here and here, $NUR.CN started as an oversized speculative bet.
To this day, having this much capital tied up in one entity that has still to prove itself execution-wise is frustrating.
In the past few days however, the company has suprisingly announced three Memorandums of Understanding:
 with Telinno Consulting in Mali (West Africa) for 150 sites with Sierra Tel in Sierra Leone (West Africa) for 125 sites with MTN in South Sudan for 250 sites  The timelines for the definitive agreements are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viemed</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/viemed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 11:33:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/viemed/</guid>
      <description>Why I&amp;rsquo;m exiting I had a small position in Viemed because it&amp;rsquo;s a company with strong growth, a strong moat and a deep runway.
I decided to sell because, for one, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be in that space anymore, i.e. selling services to dying people.
But more importantly, I initially had overlooked the compensation of top executives. Top-5 executives compensation was 7.4% of revenues in 2019. I don&amp;rsquo;t like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converge Technologies</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/cts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 17:46:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/cts/</guid>
      <description>In a nutshell Connor Haley (Alta Fox Capital) made a presentation (video and slides) about multi-baggers.
It turns out two thirds of the performance of multi-baggers comes from multiple expansion, and one third from EBITDA growth.
In the case of $CTS.TO I&amp;rsquo;ve extracted as much as I can reasonably expect from multiple expansion, and I see risk on the EBITDA front going forward.
Risk vs uncertainty I sold ~most~ all of my $CTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 2</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:08:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-2/</guid>
      <description>In my first post about Nuran, I talked a lot about my internal and external environment, internal being my feelings (frustration, envy, greed), and external being my work setting, the information I expose myself to, etc.
Today I learned two new things from Guy Spier&amp;rsquo;s book.
Commitment bias The first one is the danger that comes with publicly sharing your current positions. I already had a feeling about this one but reading Guy&amp;rsquo;s explanation and detailed examples made me realize I&amp;rsquo;m not careful enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuran - part 1</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 21:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/nuran-1/</guid>
      <description>I need to flush out everything I can about the Nuran thing. Rub my nose in it. And then hopefully come out cleaner on the other side.
This is the first post. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s the last one.
What happened I don&amp;rsquo;t remember much about the day when I bought the bulk of my Nuran position.
But I do remember the moment when I was buying. It felt like nothing else existed except for me and this stock I desired so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 12:24:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/baba/</guid>
      <description>Thesis Summary Final version (LOL):
Listen. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna pretend I understand Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s business and the risks involved. I don&amp;rsquo;t. But here&amp;rsquo;s how I think about it. If someone I consider a true master says this is a good move, and from a price perspective, the move only gets MORE attractive, then I have no problem putting some money here. If it turns out that it was not a good move, I honestly will have no bad feelings about it; for the simple reason that if the master got it wrong, then anybody else would have as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Communications Management</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 10:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/dcm/</guid>
      <description>Bottom line up front I am not taking a position in DCM as of today. While the stock is cheap in terms of multiples, the company is in the declining printing business and they need a mini-miracle to expand out of it into digital. I do not see a clear path towards a 10 bagger in 5 years.
The cannabis labeling business represents only 5% of their revenues despite their market leader position in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
