<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>portfolio on The Chief&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://chiefhustler.com/categories/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in portfolio on The Chief&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 11:09:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chiefhustler.com/categories/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - October 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-october-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 11:09:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-october-2021/</guid>
      <description>Results This month was a good one. My best year-to-date, actually.
I don&amp;rsquo;t show % returns anymore. I believe those metrics are useless for me, at this stage of my journey. My long-term goal is to be able to comfortably retire from my portfolio. Cash returns just align me better with this objective. They hit harder, and feel more concrete. The world doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to hold fiat currencies in high regard at the moment, but I like them $Dollaz$!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - August 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-august-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:11:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-august-2021/</guid>
      <description>Comments US-listed stocks now represent 22.9% of the portfolio, up from 22% the previous month. Although there are certainly some good opportunities in the US market, I have no appetite for more $USD exposure at the moment.
As I wrote last month, I have a sizeable position in $GFP.V subscription receipts. Those should convert into shares tomorrow. The stock price has dipped significantly in the last month ($1.88 today vs $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - July 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 10:22:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>Comments US-listed stocks (including $BABA) now represent 22% of the portfolio.
$NUR.CN is still weighing heavily on the performance. All the US stocks are down as well, except for the small position in $JAKK. $WELL.TO is down 15% from last month.
This month I had my first experience with rights ($GFP-RT.V). I bought as much as I felt comfortable buying, which I think was 71,500 rights plus a tiny bit of oversubscription just for practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - June 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-june-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-june-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preliminary remark I purposely refrain from sharing my portfolio updates on social media. First, because no one cares. Sharing would just put me in a position to care about the fact that no one cares, and that would be a waste of mental energy. Second, this is only my second year of investing seriously (we could even argue that 2020 doesn&amp;rsquo;t count) so there&amp;rsquo;s really not much to share anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Update - May 2021</title>
      <link>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-may-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 14:33:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chiefhustler.com/posts/update-may-2021/</guid>
      <description>Below is the portfolio&amp;rsquo;s performance YTD (time-weighted cumulative return). The month&amp;rsquo;s performances assume cashflows occured mid-month. USD holdings are excluded but quite small at the moment.
The positive performance was driven mainly by CTS.TO which has been a great holding so far (up more than 100% since first purchase), and NUR.CN which is down around 30% since first purchase but made a nice comeback this month. The big losers were PBX.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
